# Wenzhe Luo

 Vienna, VA, 22182, USA
 ■ wluo4@gmu.edu
 571-471-6209
 Github

Last semester master student in GMU with main focuses on Computer Engineering and Machine Learning. Currently have hand-on experiences in Full Stack Development and Machine Learning. Seek a Software Engineer (SDE) & Full Stack engineer.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Master of Science: Computer Engineering (GPA: 3.83/4.00)

01/2021 - 05/2023

George Mason University

- Concentration: Machine Learning and Computer Engineering (MLCE)
- Courses: Big Data Technologies, Computer Network Architecture and Protocol, Neuromorphic Computing, Advanced Mobile Systems and Applications, Machine Learning for Embedded Systems, Internet of Things (IoT)

# Bachelor of Science: Electrical Engineering and Automation (GPA: 86.4/100)

09/2013 - 06/2017

Guangzhou College of South China University of Technology

**Honor:** Outstanding undergraduate (First-class Scholarship) • *Courses: Advanced Language Programming I (C++)* 

# PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# Software engineer, Intern

09/2022 – present Vienna, United States

Meetfood ₽

- Developed object-oriented code in Node.js with 100% accordance with company standards, Designed user and activity database using MongoDB and deployed it onto mLab to ensure App's stability and persistency;
- Improved user interfaces with modern JavaScript frameworks, HTML5, and CSS3, used AWS Cognito to manage and authenticate user and identity;
- Updated 4 versions of the Me page to use JavaScript framework React.js to provide user profile cards
- Worked within an agile team to improve **Restful API design**: User APIs, and Video APIs

#### Lab in ECE of GMU (Research Assistant)

04/2022 - 05/2022

• Researched ML methods to realize 7 different Neural architectures affect fairness for Skin-Image Search

Fairfax, United States

• Implemented Scikit learn and Matplotlib, compared to PCA in visualizing dermatology datasets by using t-SNE

# **PROJECTS**

# Web App - Elevator Booking List (Independent) ∂

01/2023 - present

Built a Web App for residents in Adaire apartment to apply for using elevator and deployed the App to the Cloud

- Designed and established a user-friendly website by using Streamlit based on Python, including an optimized elevator-booking list and email-sending page;
- Built a elevators using predictive model, reviewed and developed data by using pandas and cleaned data by setting
  from .txt/ file to .xlsx/ file resulting in a decrease in the squeeze of elevator usage of 65%;
- Deployed the web App in the cloud through Heroku (PaaS), and worked closely with the apartment front desk to
  publish daily forecast elevator usage in order to optimize and increase efficiency by 80%

### MERN Stack: Website app for Hotel Reservation system (Independent)

08/2022 - 11/2022

- Built a MERN (MongoDB, Express, React (UI design), Node.js)-Stack Website App to allow users to book a hotel
  - Designed and created 8 RESTful APIs using Node.js, and wrote structured, tested, readable code;
    Developed for storing, editing, and deleting user's data in MongoDB with Insomnia, optimized 3 versions of the user
  - Developed for storing, editing, and deleting user's data in MongoDB with Insomnia, optimized 3 versions of the user login module for functional perfection;
  - Used **Bcryptjs** for hashing and storing passwords to enhance user *privacy protection*, completed the entire project using the **oop-library mongoose** with **JavaScript**.

# ML: Prediction of NBA team strength in 2023 (independent) ∂

05/2022 - 06/2022

Implemented ML Algorithm to predict the outcome of each game in the ongoing 2022-2023 NBA regular season

- Aggregated data from the web [basketball-reference], cleaned data set into CSV format, used **ELO function** to initialize the integrated data and implemented **sklearn**'s Logistic regression method to establish the regression model.
- Optimized data and visualized final results (matplotlib and seaborn) by comparing to the xGoals decision ML model (applied Amazon SageMaker to build, train, and deploy machine learning models)

# IoT: Realtime GPS Tracking System (Group Leader) &

02/2022 - 04/2022

Created an embedded lightweight device and implemented real-time data transmission with Google Firebase Cloud platform

- Connected 5 components to Arduino Nano 33 IoT and used Google Firebase as a Cloud platform;
- Improved the response of the system to ensure that the experimental results are maintained at time-difference within 0.1s and distance error within 5m(based on **C language**);
- Converted data results in txt./ form to Excel table (100% accuracy) by using **Python**

# **SKILLS**

# **Programming Languages:**

10015

**Web Development** 

Python, SQL, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, TypeScript

PyCharm, VS code, Swagger, Mock, JMeter, Redux, React, Node, Express

Database

Node.js, MongoDB, Git, Spring, Google Firebase, AWS

NoSQL(MongoDB), SQL